(Supported by MCST and KOCCA)
(This drama is purely a work of fiction.)
(All scenes with child actors and animals were filmed safely.)
(The Affair Was Just The Beginning)
(Episode 8: Second House)
Attorney Choi.
Are you okay? What's happening to you?
Are you just going to stand there?
You're doctors! Do something!
Exactly, we have two doctors right here!
Wait!
Get something to support his neck first.
- Get a grip, Joo Bo Sung! - His neck?
- Loosen his clothes here. - His neck.
What do we do? What should we do?
- What else? We take him to the hospital. - The hospital?
He's got a head injury. He needs to be treated quickly.
The police.
Let's have the police take him.
What?
- The police? - The police?
Are you out of your mind?
This is bad.
What...
Wait! Stop!
Hurry up.
We're bringing in a patient with a head injury.
We need a bed ready right now.
The door. Get the door!
- Get him in. - Stop.
Getting him to the ER comes first. Let's figure out the legal mess later.
What legal mess? This was your doing!
You stupid jerk! This is all because of you guys!
- Keep it down. Careful. - Hurry up.
Wait. You're driving?
Well, it's my car. Who else?
Are you going to stay glued to this punk?
That doesn't matter right now. Go check on Ye Ji...
Stop wasting time! If Attorney Choi dies, I'm blaming all of you!
Never mind.
I'll handle Ye Ji. You drive.
Not that she'll listen to me anyway!
Me?
What, you want him to go by himself?
Come on! Let's get moving!
That's right, stay with me. Keep breathing.
Don't stop breathing.
Darn it.
Goodness.
Why is traffic so slow?
Good heavens.
What do we do?
Let's put that off until Wednesday.
Ye Ji?
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Min Seo?
You in there?
Let's have a little chat.
Take a seat.
Sit down.
So,
tell me what you know...
about the man who died.
You were talking about it with your friend earlier.
Well, that's...
We...
- I mean, I... - I'm listening.
Nice and slow.
Well...
The thing is...
Min Seo, are you in there?
Ye Ji.
I know you're confused.
I know none of this...
makes any sense to you...
right now.
(Incoming call: My Daughter)
Min Seo.
Ye Ji?
Mom.
That guy from the demolition site knows about the accident.
He just showed up. He's demanding Min Seo...
to tell him what happened that night.
Min Seo?
Where are you...
Ye Ji?
Ye Ji...
- Hey, listen. Min Seo... - What?
- Min Seo is in danger. - What?
- What about Min Seo? Why? - Ye Ji...
just called.
- Some guy from the demolition site... - The number you dialled cannot...
knows about the accident.
And he's got...
Min Seo, she says.
What do you mean, he's got her?
Do you...
Do you know where Min Seo is?
Min...
(Live Location)
(132-43 Ihaeri-gil, Yongsin-dong)
Yongsin-dong?
Wait, isn't your vacation home there?
You're right.
It's our vacation home.
(The Zip)
Attorney Choi?
Attorney Choi...
Attorney Choi!
- No! Oh, gosh. - What is it?
He's not breathing.
Do something!
What do we do? Oh, goodness. Attorney Choi.
What do we do?
Goodness...
I won't last a single day in prison.
I'll lose my medical license.
Attorney Choi.
Say something!
It was an accident, right? Just an accident...
Attorney Choi, say something.
Oh, my.
Attorney Choi.
So, you weren't together...
on March 30?
No.
Your stories are...
Look.
Your stories aren't matching up.
Let's have some tea. It's good for the body.
Fair warning, though.
If you lie to me from here on out,
things might get...
a bit painful.
Jeez.
Sit down.
You probably thought...
you could do this to me...
because I look like a friendly guy,
but looks can be deceiving.
Got it.
I'll get there as fast as I can.
Don't go in there by yourselves.
Wait outside for me, okay?
What kind of jerk is messing with my girl?
Darn.
It can't be a kidnapping, right?
If it is, they should be asking for something.
But we haven't heard a word.
Don't you think this is weird?
Tell me.
Ye Ji said...
it's the guy from the demolition site...
and he knows about the accident.
Does that...
ring a bell?
No?
Oh, my goodness.
I know we adults aren't...
on the best terms right now,
but we need to figure out what exactly is going on,
get our stories straight,
and come up with a plan or something before we get there.
- Or do you not want to save the kids? - Who said I don't?
You're not the only one worried about them. Goodness, gracious.
I'll drop you both off up ahead, okay?
This is insane.
Fine, we're only delaying the time of death.
It's not like taking him to the ER...
will bring him back anyway.
Oh, goodness.
What should I do about Ye Ji?
This is driving me nuts.
I'm sorry, Choi Sang Cheol.
The dead man's twin brother is the one...
holding our kids hostage?
Oh, boy.
What if he took the kids...
to get revenge on us?
No way, right? It can't be that.
Which is exactly why we need to call the cops right now.
I told you, we can't let the cops near that vacation home!
Why the heck not...
Wait.
That's where you took care of...
Oh, dear.
Good heavens! Then...
My goodness.
Okay?
So,
we need to get there fast. We have to hurry.
I don't normally lay a hand...
on pregnant women or kids.
Tell me.
Who is the dead man?
I...
That man...
So, that man...
I...
Move!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
- Out! - We might get ourselves killed...
before we even reach the kids.
Seriously...
Now I know who Min Seo gets her awful driving from.
Excuse me?
If your daughter hadn't tempted her,
Min Seo would never have had to drive in the first place.
- Tempted her? - I can't believe...
she ended up dating someone like Ye Ji.
Someone like Ye Ji? What is that supposed to mean?
My daughter...
could've dated someone way prettier and nicer than Min Seo!
- Oh, my. - Jeez, this is frustrating!
Both Lim Ye Ji and Lim Jae Hong...
Darn it!
Jeez, you're...
vulgar.
So vulgar.
- Are you crazy, punk? - It's dangerous.
- Stop. - If we don't take him to the ER,
they're going to suspect me later, you jerk!
- It's dangerous. - I know...
you're doing this on purpose because I slept with your wife, jerk.
What the heck are you saying, you psycho?
If we don't go right now, your daughter will die!
- What? - Jeez.
Didn't you hear my wife?
Some lunatic is trying to kill your daughter!
Who is that darn jerk?
We need to call the police. Did you call the cops?
Enough with the cops already.
That hit-and-run Choi Sang Cheol was talking about?
It wasn't us. It was your daughter!
What?
And that punk is holding her hostage for revenge!
Jeez.
You have no idea what's going on.
Fine, call the police.
Call them...
and send your own daughter to jail yourself.
That makes no sense.
How could my daughter...
How could she...
Both Ahn Soo Jung and Park Kyung Hee...
Why did they fall for this loser?
But...
What is it about him?
It's strange.
How could she even drive?
I swear I didn't know back then...
I had no idea he had died.
If we'd gone back...
If we'd gone back, he might've lived...
Or if only the accident had never happened...
Hey, slow down.
What accident?
The car...
Car...
I'm sorry.
I mean...
Driving...
He got hit by a car.
You're awake.
We only witnessed it.
We were only there because...
You saw us feeding the cat.
But then,
a car suddenly struck him.
We were going to call the police,
but I was so scared that I said we should just leave.
You got scared?
Do you see the kids?
So, who's the culprit?
I couldn't see their face clearly.
It was really dark and...
It was dark?
And they were...
too far away.
Even so.
Even if it was dark and they were far away,
how could you not recognise your own parents?
You really think this is going to work?
Just stick to the plan.
Don't go off-book and ruin it.
Keep your mind on the kids. Only the kids.
Jeez.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I know it's too late,
but we want...
to compensate you somehow.
Of course, no amount of compensation can wash away your grief.
We'll do whatever it takes.
If there's anything you want,
please just tell us.
Mom, he thinks you...
Anything I want?
It's not my mom. She just...
My gosh! Why are you getting so mad?
Please. We're sorry. We were wrong.
We'll compensate you for everything.
They're just kids.
They made a mistake...
because they didn't know...
any better.
The kids?
Which one of them?
- What? - What?
Well...
My daughter said...
she was in the passenger seat.
She wasn't driving.
The one driving was Min...
- Min... - It wasn't my daughter!
It was their family car to begin with,
and Ye Ji was driving her dad's car...
Nonsense!
It's all on this crazy woman and her daughter.
My kid wasn't driving.
- She doesn't even know how. - My gosh. Then,
- why did you clean up the mess? - What?
I have evidence. I got it all on video.
- I... - Are you crazy?
- You've completely lost it. - Here.
I've got it right here.
- Ouch! - Here it is.
Here.
Is that my brother they're carrying?
It was just a tragic accident.
Please...
Please don't hurt the kids.
Mom!
Ye Ji.
- Mom! - Ye Ji.
Your brother.
I'm the only one...
who knows where he is.
(Calling: Babe)
Why the heck aren't they here yet?
It...
It won't move.
Come here.
What's wrong?
- What is it? - Quiet down.
- What... - Stay still for a second.
What is it?
Honey.
- Step aside. - What are you doing?
When I ram the car, dodge.
When I give the signal, run as fast as you can.
What?
Have you lost your...
We're going to get ourselves killed.
If he finds the body, we'll all be dead anyway.
Are you saying the body is actually buried down here?
Now!
Now?
- Move. - What are you doing?
- Are you crazy? - Move!
What are you doing?
(Brake support, Collision evasion)
What the? What's going on? Why...
- Hey. - Wait.
Not at this timing!
- Jeez! - Reverse it.
Back it up!
Back up!
What's wrong with this?
Hold on.
Goodness, sir. What are you...
Oh, my.
Sir!
I wasn't driving. That punk did it!
Please calm down.
You son of a gun!
Min Seo.
Kids, this...
What's this?
Ye Ji, go inside with Min Seo and lock the door.
Run away from here, okay?
- What are these for? - What do you think?
Didn't you see the look in his eyes?
He's going to kill us!
We have to try something at least.
There are four of us.
Four? You mean, us?
We've got two men with us now.
Doesn't that give us a fighting chance?
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I'm sorry...
Oh, my. We have to do something...
Oh, boy. Goodness!
Who are you people, really?
- What... - Tell me.
Us? We...
We aren't anyone. We're just ordinary people.
Let me guess. This was an accident too?
- Yes, that too. - Yes.
- That was also an accident. - It was.
I know it's hard to believe, but it was.
Let me ask you one thing.
Why did you kill Sol and Choi Sang Cheol?
Who sent you?
- Kill them? - What...
- Because of him... - Wait.
- What do you mean, who sent us? - No.
Listen, what happened to your brother was...
truly an accident caused by Min Seo.
- No! - What do you mean, no?
- These two buried Sol... - Excuse me?
- in there. - Stop talking nonsense!
- Horrible jerks. - She keeps...
- making up ridiculous stories. - No.
Fine, then.
I'll just kill all of you darn people.
- Dad! - Honey!
- Min Seo. - Kids!
- Ye Ji! - Jeez!
Hey, you little punk!
We're so sorry.
But it's really all just a huge misunderstanding.
- Honey! - Dad!
Ye Ji!
How dare you lay a finger on my kid?
What...
Do you think this is enough?
Yes.
I added one more bag this time.
Are you okay?
What do we do?
If we take him to the hospital now...
It'll complicate things...
in many ways.
Thank goodness, we stocked up on cement.
Right, honey?
(One month later)
Yes.
Look more into it and get back to me.
Okay, bye.
Sir, the registered owner of this car is Na Sol.
Is it a woman?
No, a man.
But there's no report of the car being stolen,
and his phone's been off since then, so we can't track his location.
Smells like a homicide, doesn't it?
Yes, but we won't know for sure until we pull the car up.
What's taking them so long?
Darn, when do I get to go home?
They took the dashcam's memory card.
They removed the aftermarket one,
but the factory one is still there.
- The factory one? - Here.
It has a built-in one,
but it's outdated, so he added a custom one.
We won't know...
if the built-in camera captured anything...
until we extract the data.
If we restore the data, can we get some footage?
We'll have to give it a try.
Sir.
- Sir. - What?
- About the car owner, Na Sol. - What about him?
He has a twin brother...
named Na Do.
Apparently, they ran a private detective agency together.
- A private detective agency? - Yes.
The thing is, he is also missing.
There's been zero activity on his phone and credit cards.
Both of them?
Track down their last known locations first.
Last known locations, got it.
Honey.
Honey!
Did you see this?
You need to see this.
A mid-sized sedan is being recovered from a reservoir.
The vehicle's owner was identified...
- as a private detective. - Isn't that him?
He's been missing for 34 days.
- Mr. Na was last seen... - Yes.
- near an intersection convenience store. - The date matches.
Police launched an investigation,
- but he still... - A reservoir?
What's that about?
The police aren't...
going to show up at our door, are they?
Should we get our stories straight just in case?
If the police ask questions...
What?
This is the Cheongnam Police.
Could you open the door?
Is anyone home?
You don't remember?
Still?
You were the last people with Mr. Na Do.
Around 5pm on April 8,
you were at your vacation home, right?
This footage is from right outside your vacation home.
It's fine if you want to exercise your right to remain silent,
but if you refuse to cooperate,
I'll have to secure a warrant...
and raid that property.
I'll tell you everything.
You should.
Honey.
The truth is...
To tell you the truth...
I...
Mr. Na Do...
Jae Hong...
That's Eun Bin's real name.
Jae Hong was cheating on me with the neighbour across the road.
What...
What is this? They're...
Mr. Na discovered...
that the neighbour named Ahn Soo Jung...
and Jae Hong...
were going to the vacation home.
He got there ahead of them.
And I followed.
(Ye Ji's House)
Wow, you're so good.
Really?
Hong!
Hey, Lim Jae Hong!
But then,
is Mr. Na...
dead?
What makes you think so?
Well, you said...
we were the last ones to see him.
To be precise,
his official status is missing.
Have you perhaps...
seen this man before,
or did Mr. Na ever mention the name Ko Du Sik?
I'm not so sure...
Why do you ask?
I said it wasn't me.
Why the heck is everyone coming after me?
- We have solid evidence... - You have no...
that he planned to kill Mr. Na.
- Evidence of murder? - What...
Evidence of murder?
Yes.
Ko Du Sik tried to make contact with Mr. Na...
on the day of the incident.
It looks like he tailed Mr. Na's car.
He caused a collision on purpose...
likely with the intent to kill Mr. Na.
Darn.
You took good care of the car, right?
Yes.
Where did you dump it?
Same place as last time.
What the heck?
What was that?
- We're investigating his whereabouts after that. - Goodness.
- Gosh. - It hurts.
Once you get him on the phone, he might talk.
- So, Choi Sang Cheol and Ko Du Sik are accomplices? - I know nothing.
- I have nothing to tell. - That's right.
Oh, right. We were lucky enough...
to recover the data from that built-in dashcam.
We reviewed the footage, and the results show...
(March 31, 2026)
Let's see...
What is this?
Take a look at this.
- Wait. - What is this?
The footage confirms that Choi Sang Cheol murdered Na Sol.
That's exactly why Na Do was tracking him.
So, this is the hallway of the hostess bar,
- and you showed this to Mr. Na Do, right? - Yes.
Na Do was looking for Choi Sang Cheol, right?
Yes, he was.
That's when you showed him this CCTV footage?
Yes, but I just showed it to him because he asked to see it.
Given the circumstances, it looks like he took revenge.
And Ko Du Sik killed Na Do?
We don't have solid proof yet,
but yes.
Find the evidence and bring it to me.
Yes, sir.
But Chief,
there isn't a single trace left behind this time.
Ko Du Sik is no ordinary thug.
That darn punk.
- Hey. - Yes, sir.
If we lose him again, we'll both be stripped of our badges.
Understood, sir.
What do you mean, there's no evidence?
- Gyeong Tae. - It's Song Gyeong Tae, sir.
- Find evidence. - Yes, sir.
Bring it to me even if you have to fabricate it.
- Yes, sir. - Good.
Goodbye, sir.
- Sir. - What?
What should we do about them?
Leak it to the press.
I'm drowning in work here. You should know how to handle this by now.
(A respected and loved police force)
Have a good day.
(Fair and kind police for the citizens)
(Cha Eun Bin in Affair with a Dermatologist)
(Actor Cha Eun Bin, currently at the peak of his career...)
(We sincerely apologize.)
(We're sorry for causing you such disappointment and pain.)
This is Park Kyung Hee.
The recent reports...
about my husband's affair...
have caused great disappointment and discomfort to so many of you.
I know better than anyone...
that there's no excuse...
for what happened.
I don't believe...
I'm free from responsibility...
in this, either.
(Just delete the channel.)
(Crystal Dermatology Clinic? That's my neighbourhood.)
(Park Kyung Hee is a saint. Cha Eun Bin is trash.)
(Report)
(Wrong information)
(Didn't Park Kyung Hee take him back anyway?)
Once upon a time, two close families...
lived in a beautiful and peaceful town.
(Gallery)
(My albums)
(Data)
They always kept each other in their thoughts.
(April 9, 2026, 6:18pm)
They trusted and cared for each other...
- more than anyone else. - Let's go.
They lived happily ever after.
- Thanks. - No problem, ma'am.
(The Zip)
(Captain Park on the Move)
(Park Kyung Hee)
(Cheongnam Crystal Dermatology)
(Temporarily Closed)
All right. Just a moment.
Dr. Joo.
Should we prepare for the next patient right away?
Yes.
(Ahn Soo Jung: The payment is overdue. Send the money now.)
Seriously...
No, it's nothing. We're all done here.
You're good to go.
Unbelievable.
It's not like I owe her anything.
(Transfer complete: 15 million won to Ahn Soo Jung)
(Ahn Soo Jung, Park Kyung Hee: 15 million won)
They dumped the car in the reservoir on purpose.
It was to destroy the evidence so no one would find it.
So, they ran the private detective agency together?
Yes, the twins ran it together.
But they both went missing?
They didn't really have anyone close to them,
so no one even noticed their disappearance.
Where could...
the missing twins have vanished to?
And what exactly was inside the car pulled from the reservoir?
The truth behind the missing twins.
It will be revealed at 10pm on Wednesday.
Getting rid of a 120kg athletic guy without a single trace?
It's highly likely this was done by a professional.
Honey, hurry.
That being said, we need to focus on some new figures here.
In the past, Choi Sang Cheol defended Ko Du Sik in a murder trial.
(Murder Defence, Accomplice)
Ko Du Sik was acquitted,
- What? - and the two formed...
- Why is Ko Du Sik in this? - a close bond.
Ko Du Sik definitely attacked Na Do that day.
And then, the smoking gun surfaced.
This is an exclusive video obtained by "News Papa."
Viewer discretion is advised.
("News Papa")
Darn it.
(The Affair Was Just The Beginning)